{
    "subject": "resource/RocknRolla",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:French_films",
    "human_readable": "RocknRolla is about French films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9849488139152527,
            "question": "Is RocknRolla a French film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.898222804069519,
            "question": "Does the film RocknRolla explore French cinematic traditions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8954609036445618,
            "question": "Can you describe the theme of RocknRolla in relation to French films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8389804363250732,
            "question": "How does RocknRolla compare to other films about French culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.81654953956604,
            "question": "Are there any prominent French actors or directors involved in RocknRolla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7242442965507507,
            "question": "What is the subject of the film RocknRolla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7186185121536255,
            "question": "What type of films are associated with RocknRolla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6148302555084229,
            "question": "What is the genre of the film RocknRolla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5486020445823669,
            "question": "What country's cinema is RocknRolla connected to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.316455602645874,
            "question": "What are some potential cultural insights viewers might gain from watching RocknRolla?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=RocknRolla is about French films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2741_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country's cinema is RocknRolla connected to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2741_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the genre of the film RocknRolla?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2741_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of films are associated with RocknRolla?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2741_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2741_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2741_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2741_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2741_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2741_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2741_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2741_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2741_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2741_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2741_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents discuss the movie \"RocknRolla\" directed by Guy Ritchie and do not mention it being about French films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}